(Leonard:)Problem?
(Howard:)This is the worst cobbler
I've ever eaten.
It tastes like it's made of
actual ground-up shoemaker.
(Sheldon:)Amusing. A play on the
two meanings of "cobbler."
(Raj:)Hey, guys. Guess who
I found at LAX?
(Raj:)My baby sister Priya.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, I object.
(Sheldon:)You propose a guessing game,
(Sheldon:)yet you don't give me
enough time to guess.
(Sheldon:)For the record,
I was going to say:
"Your sister Priya."
(Priya:)Oh, Sheldon. You haven't
changed a bit, have you?
(Sheldon:)Why would I change?
(Leonard:)The hope has been that
(Leonard:)you'd eventually bend
to public opinion.
(Leonard:)So, Priya, what brings
you back to L.A.?
I have a one-day layover
on my way to Toronto.
(Priya:)Corporate merger.
(Raj:)Can you believe it?
(Raj:)Little Priya's one
of the lead attorneys
(Raj:)for the biggest
car company in India.
(Sheldon:)Given that when we met her,
she was finishing law school
(Sheldon:)and planning an internship
at a large Indian car company,